A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Public Broadcasting, Program Files FA580
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Public Broadcasting, Program Files
1965-1968
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA580
1.2 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Alphabetical
Scope and Contents
Contains correspondence, memoranda, photographs and administrative records.
Ford Foundation
- Fisher, John -- NET Consultant, 1965 (Box 1)
- Fitch, John T., 1967 (Box 1)
- Frankel, Max -- NET Consultant, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- The George Washington University Communications System Planning Institute, 1967 (Box 1)
- House of Representatives, 1967 (Box 1)
- Hurley, Father -- Chile International Education via Satellite, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- Instructional Television with Special Reference to American Samoa -- Bowles, 1966 (Box 1)
- Instructional Television in Italy -- Crossland, 1966 (Box 1)
- University of the Air -- ITV, 1967 (Box 1)
- Killian, James, 1967 (Box 1)
- Kimball, Solon T. -- NET Consultant, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Levin, Harvey -- Broadcast Licenses and Case for Taxation, 1967 (Box 1)
- Mister Roger's Neighborhood -- NET Program Children's Show, 1968 (Box 1)
- MPATI, 1967 (Box 1)
- NAB, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
- NAEB (1/2), 1964-1967 (Box 2)
- NAEB (2/2), 1965-1967 (Box 2)
- Parsons, James O., Jr., 1968 (Box 2)
- Pechman, Joseph, 1967 (Box 2)
- Photographs -- Martin Luther King Assassination, 1968 (Box 2)
- Pritchard, W.L., 1967 (Box 2)
- Public Broadcast Laboratory -- Comments on PBL Broadcasts, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
- Rourke, Francis -- NET Consultant, 1965-1966 (Box 2)